A Guide to the Records of the Arlington Heritage Alliance, Inc., 1976-2006
Arlington Public Library, Center for Local History
- Victor E. Muniec Files
  - Photographs
    - Ballston, apartment buildings at Wilson Boulvevard and N. Monroe Street, May 2001 (Box 26)
    - Clarendon Common Market, construction and grand opening, 2001 (Box 26)
    - Wilson Boulevard in Clarendon, May 2001 (Box 26)
      - View from Common Grounds (on a rainy day)
      - N. Kansas Street between Wilson Blvd. and Fairfax Drive
      - 3300 block of Wilson Blvd.
      - 3400 block of Wilson Blvd.
      - 3500 block of Wilson Blvd.
    - Rosslyn, 2001-2002 (Box 26)
      - Construction underway in Rosslyn
      - Bromptons at N. Quinn Street & Clarendon Blvd.
      - Swansen Apartments at Rhodes & 16th Street
      - Rosslyn
    - Cherrydale, December 18, 2001 (Box 26)
      - Lee Highway/South side just above Route 66
    - Ballston-Virginia Square, January 17, 2002 (Box 26)
      - Construction near Virginia Square Metro
    - Construction in Arlington, February 11, 2002 (Box 26)
      - Rear addition to old house
      - Townhouses under consturction at Lee Highway & Adams St.
      - Townhouse units in back of Clarendon Market Common
    - Historic House, April 1998 (Box 26)
      - Historic House opposite Arlington Hospital, demolished in 2001
    - General Olmsted House, February 2000 (Box 26)
    - Clarendon, 1990-2000 (Box 26)
      - Wilson Blvd.
      - [Flea Market Store]
      - [Washington Blvd. Motors]
      - Back of New Delhi Cafe
      - St. Charles [Borromeo Catholic] Church
      - Clarendon
      - Hahn Building
    - Fort C. F. Smith, 1996-2001 (Box 26)
      - AHA "Progress" Program at Ft. C. F. Smith with Sherm Pratt, Myron Blackwell and Judith Muniec
      - Ft. C. F. Smith, walking tour co-sponsored by Arlington Heritage Alliance and the Arlington Historical Society
      - Manor House
      - Exhibit in Manor House
    - Historic Buidlings and Sites, various dates (Box 26)
      - The Glebe House, 1820, 4527 17th Street N.
      - Arlington Post Office, 1937, 3118 Washington Boulevard
      - Dan Kain Buidling, 1945, 3100 Washington Blvd.
      - Matthew F. Maury School, 1910, 3550 Wilson Blvd.
      - Clarendon Citizens Hall, 1921, 3211 Wilson Blvd.
      - Eastman-Fenwick House, 1876, 6733 Lee Highway
      - Glenmore, 1906, 3440 N. Roberts Lane
      - Harry Crossman House, 1892, 2501 N. Underwood Street
      - Hume School, 2891, 1805 S. Arlington Ridge Road
      - Carlin Community Hall, 1892, 5711 4th Street S.
      - Ball Sellers House, 1760, 5625 3rd Street S.
      - BAll Sellers House, 1760, 5620 3rd Street S.
      - Ball Family Burial Grounds, 1814, 3427 Washington Boulevard
      - Ball Family Burial Grounds, 1814, 3427 Washington Boulevard
      - Ball-Carlin Cemetery, 1785, 300 S. Kensington Street
      - Travers Family Graveyard, 1830, 1309 S. Monroe Street
      - Alcova, 1860, 3435 8th Street S.
      - Fort Ethan Allen, 1861, 3829 N. Stafford Street
      - Walker Chapel and Cemetery, 1871, 4102 N. Glebe Road
      - Maywood Neighborhood Historic District, 1909
      - Maywood Neighborhood Historic District, 1909
      - Abingdon Plantation Ruins
      - Barcroft Community House, 1907, 800 S. Buchanan Street
      - Harry Gray House, 1881, 1005 S. Quinn Street
      - Lomax AME Zion Church, 1922, 2705 24th Road S.
      - Clarendon
      - Clarendon
      - Abbey Mausoleum, Fort Myer
      - Hahn-Lerner Building
    - Lawyers' Row, Destruction, [n.d.] (Box 26)
      - Across from Arlington Court House
      - Mekong Center (Hahn Building)
    - Clarendon and Ballston, various dates (Box 26)
      - Judy Muniec and unidentified man in field
      - Kirkwood & Washington Boulevard
      - Virginia Square Metro
      - Wilson Blvd., Al's Motors
      - Pollard Garden site on Wilson
      - View of section of Clarendon from Washington Blvd.
      - View from front of Sears Tire
      - Pentagon City area, Borders
      - Clarendon, Townhouses at Washignton Blvd. & Kirkwood
      - Lyon Park
      - Clarendon
      - Site for George Mason University
      - Blockbuster Building, Clarendon Boulevard
      - [Precision Tune Auto Care]
      - Gas Station, Precision Tune
    - Arlington Backyard Gardens Tour, June 6, 1992 (Box 26)
      - Sponsored by AHA
    - Roundtable with Connie Ramirez, 2006 (Box 26)
    - AHA Annual Meeting, 2006 (Box 26)
      - Arlington Arts Center
    - Grey House Potters, 2006 (Box 26)
      - 5509 Wilson Boulevard
    - Upton Hill, November 2001 (Box 26)
      - Wilson Boulevard
    - Cherrydale house, [n.d.] (Box 26)
      - Cherrydale
    - Cathedral of St. Thomas More, [n.d.] (Box 26)
      - 3901 Cathedral Lane
    - Clarendon, 1991 (Box 26)
      - T. A. Sullivan Monuments
      - Washington Boulevard
    - Ball-Carlin Cemetery, 1991 (Box 26)
    - American Red Cross Building, [1994-1995] (Box 26)
      - 4833 Arlington Blvd.
    - Ballston, Demolition of 3813 14th Street N., April 1999 (Box 26)
      - Demolition of 3813 14th St. N.
    - Colonial Village, 1999 (Box 26)
      - Queens Lane & N. Rhodes Street
      - Queens Lane & N. Rhodes Street
    - Clarendon, Post Office, November 2009 (Box 27)
    - Glebe Park, December 2000 (Box 27)
      - 4211 N. Old Glebe Road
    - Abbey Mausoleum, February 2001 (Box 27)
      - View just before Arlington County permitted destruction
    - Navy League Building, May 15, 2001 (Box 27)
      - Building and Housing Complex at 2300 Wilson Boulevard
    - Ford Barnard, May 2001 (Box 27)
    - AHA Meetings, 2000-2001 (Box 27)
      - AHA Christmas Dinner at Ft. Myer Officers Club
      - Farewell to Kate Comeau (Board member) - Laura, Shannon Bell, Kate, no name, Margaret (2 copies)
      - AHA annual meeting at Clarendon Ballroom
    - HALRB Awards Ceremony, May 20, 2001 (Box 27)
      - Common Grounds Coffee and Tea House, Jay Fisette, speaker
    - Music at Clarendon Market, May 31, 2001 (Box 27)
    - Ball House, Appraisal of Antiques, 2001 (Box 27)
    - Oatlands Conference, September 24, 2001 (Box 27)
      - Oatlands Conference on historic organization of Northern Virginia cooperation
    - AHA Meeting, October 1, 2001 (Box 27)
      - AHA meeting
    - AHS-AHA Meeting, November 8, 2001 (Box 27)
      - Central Library, Dr. Stephen Fuller (GMU), Speaker
    - AHA Dinner and Reception, December 7, 2001 (Box 27)
      - Clarendon Ballroom and reception at the Muniecs
    - Arlington Arts Center Celebration, [2001] (Box 27)
    - Clarendon, 2001 (Box 27)
      - View of McCaffrey project
      - View from Highland & 10th St.
      - Clarendon Metro Station